http://www.chorusamerica.org/terms-of-use

Skip to main content
Terms of Use
Chorus America ("CA") is a nonprofit organization.  The mission of CA is to build a dynamic and inclusive choral community so that more people are transformed by the beauty and power of choral singing. CA offers a wide range of articles, templates, programs, and services to strengthen choruses throughout the US and Canada.
By using, browsing or accessing our web site located at www.chorusamerica.org (the "Site") and the services offered on the Site (such services, collectively with the Site, the "Services"), you agree to be bound by these Terms of Use and the terms of our Privacy Policy, located at https://chorusamerica.org/privacy-policy, as in effect at the time you access the Site.
Use Guidelines
You agree to use the Services solely for not-for-profit or educational purposes. You shall not reproduce, sell, resell, distribute or exploit for any purpose other than for your own personal use, any portion of the Services. You may not: (a) access the Services using any high volume or automated means or (b) place pop-up windows over Site pages, or otherwise affect the display of Site pages.
You agree not to use the Services to: (a) violate any law, (b) impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity, (c) stalk, harass or harm another individual, (d) promote intolerance toward any protected class, (e) collect or store personal data about other users or visitors to the Site, (f) disobey any requirements, procedures, policies or regulations of networks connected to the Services, or interfere with or disrupt the Services, the Site or servers or networks connected to the Site, (g) upload, post or otherwise transmit any Content that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright, or other proprietary rights of any party or Content that is designed to interrupt, destroy, or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment or (h) intentionally or unintentionally violate any applicable local, state, national or international law.
You acknowledge that CA does not pre-screen all of the Content on the Site, but that CA and its designees shall have the right (but not the obligation) in their sole discretion to remove or refuse to remove any Content that is available through the Service. Without limiting the foregoing, CA and its designates shall have the right, but not the obligation, to remove any content that violates the Terms of Use or is otherwise objectionable, or that infringes or is alleged to infringe intellectual property rights. You agree that you must evaluate, and bear all risks associated with, the use of any content, including any reliance on the accuracy, completeness, security, or usefulness of such content. Furthermore, CA reserves the right to limit access to the Site, if found in violation of the Terms of Service.
Account registration and verification, and payment are required in order to create a Chorus America Membership Account ("Account"). During registration for the Account, all users are required to provide accurate, complete and current information about themselves or their organization in all required fields. Should any of the information change after submitting it to CA, you are required to update that information as soon as possible. Should CA suspect that your personal or organizational information is not complete, current, or accurate, your Account may be subject to suspension or termination. Should you feel that the privacy policy is not sufficient for you to complete the registration form truthfully, please email your policy concerns to service@chorusamerica.org. Users under 13 years of age are required to have a parent or guardian review and complete the registration process.
Proprietary Materials
All materials contained on the Site are Copyright © Chorus America, are licensed or otherwise published by CA with the permission of the owner of the material, or are licensed by the individuals posting such materials on the Site. All rights in such materials are reserved to the respective owners.
No materials contained on the Site may be copied, modified, published, broadcast, or otherwise distributed without our prior written permission. Any reproduction permitted under these Terms of Use must contain the following notice: "Copyright © [Year] Chorus America. All rights reserved."
The information contained on the Site, as well as the design and layout of the Site, contains elements protected by trademark, trade dress, copyright, or other laws, and may not be copied or imitated in whole or in part. No text, logo, graphic, sound, or image from the Site may be copied or retransmitted without the express written permission of CA except as incidentally necessary to use this Site and with the following exception: members may download and display the CA logo in online and print materials without written permission.
Intellectual Property Rights of Others
We respect the intellectual property rights of others and request that our visitors do the same. Pursuant to Section 512(c) of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA), Title 17, United States Code, a copyright owner or its authorized agent may submit a notification for believed copyright infringement based on material that is residing on the Site.
If you think your work has been copied in a manner that constitutes copyright infringement, you may notify our copyright agent, who can be reached at:
Chorus America
1156 15th Street NW, Ste 310
Washington, DC 20005
The notification must include ALL of the following:
A physical or electronic signature of the copyright owner or the person authorized to act on the owner's behalf;
a description of the copyrighted work you claim has been infringed;
a description of where the material you claim is infringing is located on this Site;
your name, address, telephone number, email address and all other information reasonably sufficient to permit CA to contact you;
a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law; and
a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
If you believe that content has been taken down improperly from the Site or that access to material on the Site was improperly disabled, you may send a counter-notification to the CA copyright agent identified above. Such counter-notification must contain the following information:
Your physical or electronic signature, or that of an authorized representative;
a description of the material that you claim has been improperly removed or to which you believe access has been improperly disabled and the location at which the material appeared before it was removed or access was disabled;
a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that you have a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or misidentification of the material to be removed or disabled;
your name, address and telephone number, and a statement that (i) you consent to the jurisdiction of the federal district court for the judicial district in which such address is located or, if your address is outside of the United States, to any judicial district in which CA may be found, and (ii) you will accept service of process from the claimant who provided CA's designated agent with notification of the alleged infringement in accordance with the DMCA, or an agent of such person.
Warranties
YOUR USE OF THIS SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THIS SITE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO RESTRICT OR TERMINATE YOUR ACCESS TO THIS SITE OR ANY FEATURE OR PART THEREOF AT ANY TIME. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, CA EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND ANY WARRANTIES THAT MATERIALS ON THIS SITE ARE NONINFRINGING; THAT ACCESS TO THIS SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE; THAT THIS SITE WILL BE SECURE; THAT THIS SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES THIS SITE AVAILABLE WILL BE VIRUS-FREE; OR THAT INFORMATION ON THIS SITE WILL BE COMPLETE, ACCURATE OR TIMELY.  IF YOU DOWNLOAD ANY MATERIALS FROM THIS SITE, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK.  YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIALS.  NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM CA OR THROUGH OR FROM THIS SITE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.  CA DOES NOT MAKE ANY WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OF THE MATERIALS ON THIS SITE IN TERMS OF THEIR COMPLETENESS, CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, ADEQUACY, USEFULNESS, TIMELINESS, RELIABILITY, SAFENESS, OR OTHERWISE.
IN CERTAIN STATES, THE LAW MAY NOT PERMIT THE DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE DISCLAIMER MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Limitation of Liability
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT NEITHER CA, NOR ANY OF ITS AFFILIATES OR THIRD-PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES RELATING TO OR RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE OR ANY OTHER SITE YOU ACCESS THROUGH A LINK FROM THIS SITE OR FROM ANY ACTIONS WE TAKE OR FAIL TO TAKE AS A RESULT OF EMAIL MESSAGES YOU SEND US. THESE INCLUDE DAMAGES FOR ERRORS, OMISSIONS, INTERRUPTIONS, DEFECTS, DELAYS, COMPUTER VIRUSES, YOUR LOSS OF PROFITS, LOSS OF DATA, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO AND ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS AND DATA, AND OTHER TANGIBLE AND INTANGIBLE LOSSES.
THIS LIMITATION APPLIES REGARDLESS OF WHETHER THE DAMAGES ARE CLAIMED UNDER THE TERMS OF A CONTRACT, AS THE RESULT OF NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE ARISE OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE, INABILITY TO USE, OR PERFORMANCE OF THE INFORMATION, SERVICES, PRODUCTS OR MATERIALS AVAILABLE FROM THIS SITE, AND EVEN IF WE OR OUR REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN NEGLIGENT OR HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
BECAUSE SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY LASTS, OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, ALL OR A PORTION OF THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
External Links, Users, Sponsors and Advertisers
Links provided to other locations or sites are made available for your convenience only and do not indicate endorsement by CA of such other location or site or its information. The existence of a link to another site does not imply that the organization or person publishing at that site endorses any of the materials at the Site. CA is not responsible for the materials contained at any web site linked to the Site. You agree that CA is not responsible or liable for any loss or damage incurred as a result of any interaction or relationship with other users, sponsors, or advertisers, or as a result of any such person's or entity's access to and use of the Services.
Data Postings
Portions of the Site may allow users to post their own material. The materials posted by users do not necessarily reflect the views of CA. By posting materials to the Site, you represent that you have all necessary rights in and to such materials, and that such materials will not infringe on any personal or proprietary rights of any third parties, nor will such materials be harmful, defamatory, unlawful, threatening, obscene, lewd, lascivious, harassing, or otherwise objectionable. All information that you provide to us shall be true, accurate, and current.
CA reserves the right, at its sole discretion, for any reason or no reason whatsoever, to review, edit, or delete any material posted by users, including, without limitation, any material that CA determines may be harmful, defamatory, unlawful, threatening, obscene, lewd, lascivious, harassing, potentially in violation of any party's rights, or otherwise objectionable.
NOTWITHSTANDING THE FOREGOING, CA EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY MATERIAL COMMUNICATED BY THIRD PARTIES THROUGH THE SITE.
By posting materials to the Site, you hereby grant to CA a perpetual, non-exclusive license to use, reproduce, prepare derivative works of, distribute, perform and display any such materials in any manner or medium and sub-license such rights to any third party. You may not advertise or solicit on the Site without CA's express permission.
Privacy
If you provide personal information to us, all uses of your personal information will be treated according to our Privacy Policy located at https://chorusamerica.org/privacy-policy. By using the Site and the Services, you are accepting the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy. If you object to having your information used as described in the Privacy Policy, your sole recourse is to discontinue using the Services.
Modification to the Services and Terms of Use
CA reserves the right to modify or discontinue the Services with or without notice or liability to you or any third party. CA may change these Terms of Use from time to time and will notify you of any such changes by posting a notice of such changes on the Site.
If you object to any such changes, your sole recourse shall be to cease using the Services. Continued access to and/or use of the Services following notice of such modifications or changes shall indicate your assent to and acceptance of the Terms of Use, including, but not limited to, all posted changes.
Termination
CA reserves the right to terminate your use of any or all of the Services at any time, for any reason, including, without limitation, violation of these Terms of Use. You agree that CA shall not be liable to you or any third party for termination of your access to the Services.
Indemnification
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless CA, its affiliates and their respective directors, officers, trustees, employees, independent contractors and agents from and against any losses, liabilities, costs, and expenses (including reasonable attorneys' fees) arising out of or relating to any claim, suit, judgment, or proceeding brought or asserted by any third party arising out of or relating to (a) your violation of these Terms of Use or the rights of any other user, (b) your use of the Services, (c) any information submitted or transmitted by you through the Services, (d) your transmission of computer viruses, worms, harmful program routines or other similar items into the Site, or (e) your use of the Services to access, without authorization, any other computer or machine. CA shall have sole control over any such defense.
Governing Law
These Terms of Use shall be governed by the laws of the District of Columbia, without regard to its conflicts of law provisions.
Miscellaneous
These Terms of Use contain the entire terms between the parties. In the event any provision of these Terms of Use is held to be illegal, invalid or unenforceable, then such provision shall be severed from these Terms of Use while the remaining terms shall remain binding on the parties hereto. CA's failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action brought by you arising out of or related to the use of the Services, or specified in these Terms of Use, must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose, or shall be forever barred.
User menu
Cart
Get News
Please enter your email *
Subscribe
